

SITE RELIABILITY ENGINEER - CI/CD PIPELINE ENGINEER

■ afnazrie@gmail.com ・ 😭 site.mangkoran.com ・ 🖸 mangkoran ・ 🚾 notmangkoran ・ 🛅 mangkoran

I am an undergraduate currently studying Computer Network and Security. I am highly interested in the field of DevOps Engineering and Cloud Native Computing . I have experience working with remote teams in an organization projects. I posses a strong combination of team working, problem solving, technical skills, and curiosity with good communication abilities.

Key skills_____

Systems and Development Unix/Linux systems engineering and administration, software development,

configuration management, CI/CD pipeline development.

Cloud Native Computing AWS and GCP architecture and infrastructure development, Kubernetes ad-

ministration and monitoring.

Programming Languages and Libraries Golang, Rust, C/C++, JavaScript/TypeScript (React, Next.js, Express, Node),

Elisp

Experience _____

AccelByte Aug 2022 – Feb 2023 Indonesia

JUNIOR SITE RELIABILITY ENGINEER INTERN - LIVEOPS

Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

- · Troubleshooted and resolved technical issues in real-time.
- · Supported the deployment and testing of new releases and updates.
- · Participated in incident post-mortems and continuous improvement activities.
- · Participated in on-call rotation and became available for off-hours support as needed.
- · Monitored and maintained the performance and availability of live systems and services.
- · Managed incidents and escalations, including communication with internal stakeholders.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science, Universiti Teknologi Malaysia

Malaysia

Computer Network and Security

Sep 2019 - Present

- CGPA: 3.86
- · Dean's List: Semester 1-7

Languages _____

Bahasa Indonesia Native

English Good proficiency (IELTS band 7.0)

Bahasa Melayu Modest proficiency

APRIL 26, 2023 AFIQ NAZRIE RABBANI